where the books come to life!
Escape from Mr. Lemoncello's Library is a family, fantasy,
tv movie film directed by Scott McAboy.
Can twelve 12-year-olds escape from the most
ridiculously brilliant library ever created?
Escape from Mr.
Lemoncello's Library plunks a dozen sixth-graders into the middle of a
futuristic library for a night of nonstop fun and adventure.
Kyle Keeley, played by Casey Simpson.
Akimi Hughes, played by Breanna Yde.
Sierra Russell, played by Klarke Pipkin.
Andrew Peckelman, played by AJ Rivera.
Mr. Luigi L. Lemoncello, played by Russell Roberts.
Charles Chiltington, played by Ty Nicolas Consiglio.
Escape from Mr.
Lemoncello's Library is a 2017 film by Nickelodeon that is based on the New York Times
Best Selling Book by Chris Grabenstein's 2013 book of the same name.
The film, was directed by Scott McAboy and produced by Amy Sydorick,
starring Casey Simpson, Breanna Yde, Klarke Pipkin, A.J.
Louis Rivera Jr., and Russell Roberts.
The tone is lighthearted.